Zyad Muhammed

Software Developer

Software developer with Bachelor's degree in Computer Science and familiarity with several programming languages, and I have +2 years experience. Seeking for the position of a Programmer to utilize teamwork and leadership skills in coordinating the effort of programmers. Also, bringing exceptional skills in designing, coding, testing, and implementing customizations to exceed customer expectations.

xyadelashwal32@gmail.com

Cairo, cairo, Egypt

github.com/zyadelashwal

01060080362

in linkedin.com/in/zyad-el-ashwal-18ab6ab7

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Developer Integral, Oman

11/2020 - Present

Muscat,Oman

Develop

 Correspondence Management System in Ministry of Education Oman . Using ASP.NET, JQuery , Telerik Kendoo for frontend functionalities, c# for APIS, and Sql Server database. MyRole (Full Stack)

Contact: Eng.Ahmed Fahmy - afahmy@intergal.com.om

Software Developer

Technology Busniss Solution (TBS)

10/2019 - 11/2021

Muscat, Oman

Develop

- Tabeeb Oman Mobile using React Native. MyRole (Front End)
- Tabeeb Oman Website using React. MyRole (Front End)
- Hospital Management System using Asp.net Webservices, Jquery, Telerik, sqlserver. MyRole (Full Stack)
- ERP phramcy system using asp.net core Blazor. MyRole (Full Stack)

Contact: Eng.Wael Hosni - wael@technology-bs.com

SKILLS



ACHIEVEMENTS

React Hooks (LinkedIn Course)

React: Testing and Debugging

LANGUAGES

Arabic

English

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Professional Working Proficiency

EDUCATION

Computer Science

Computer and infomration, Suez Canal Ismalia

09/2014 - 06/2018

Egypt , ismalia

Graduation project

 Eduction Bot Chat by using ionic framework